Kaique Quilles Gomes

Brazilian, São Paulo, SP - Brazil



Email: kaiqueqg@gmail.com Site: https://kaiqueqg.github.io/cv/ Linkedin: /kaiquequillesgomes

Full-stack Developer with over 12 years of professional experience in C/C++, C# .NET (Framework, NET Core and .NET 6), ReactJS, JavaScript, CSS, SASS, Typescript, SQL Server, and general knowledge in MongoDB, React Native and Angular.

Recently, I have been expanding my skills in the cloud area, such as **AWS Services** (Lambda, API Gateway, DynamoDB, SNS, SQS), while also delving into **DevOps** practices using **Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins and Terraform.**

I am fluent in English, intermediate in French, and beginning to learn Italian.

To demonstrate my knowledge, I developed a personal project that is available on kaiqueqg.github.io/cv.

Professional Experience

BTG Pactual

Software Developer - Nov 2023 - Jan 2024

• Worked as a full-stack Cloud AWS Services C# .NET, ReactJs developer.

ACRELEC

Software Developer - Jan 2021 - Mar 2022

- Collaborated in developing a Point of Sale (POS) system for burger joints to manage orders, send requests to the kitchen, and process payments.
- As a full-stack developer, my main responsibilities included enhancing the system by developing new features and redesigning
 the user interface (UI) using ReactJS, as well as integrating with a mobile ordering system.
- Additionally, I worked on implementing promotion and discount features, fixing order handling errors in Python, and optimizing MySQL database queries.
- We daily followed agile methodologies, such as Sprints and Kanban, focusing on requirement gathering, assigning points to tasks, and conducting rigorous testing to ensure system quality.

ITAÚ

Software Developer - Sep 2019 - Nov 2020

• I served as a **full-stack** developer, working on new requirements and maintaining the existing system used by the team responsible for the security of all Itaú bank branches. I mainly worked on the back-end in **C# NET** with patterns such as **DDD** and **Repository**, front-end in **Javascript**, and used **SQL Server** database. The work involved **Sprints** with Fibonacci scoring.

Additionally, I independently performed tasks, such as:

- A state machine to replace the manual work of employees who manually selected which companies could schedule visits to the branches. The software had to accept or reject maintenance requests from other companies to Itaú bank branches based on a complex flowchart previously established with the area management.
- A state machine to replace the manual work that took weeks at the end of every year, involving several employees to re-register
 service and equipment suppliers for the branches. The software re-registered thousands of suppliers, revealing inconsistencies in
 previous registrations, requiring adjustments as the re-registration had a deadline.
- Software to manipulate another system for sending precautionary warning messages during the COVID-19 period to selected branches.

AFRESP

Software Developer - May 2018 - Sep 2019

• Developed a system in **C# Windows Forms and SQL Server** used internally for controlling information on health plans and other benefits used by the Tax Auditors associated with the association.

RDI SOFTWARE

Software Developer - Jul 2014 - Jun 2015

- Primarily worked on developing and maintaining the software used by McDonald's worldwide for kitchen and restaurant order
 management. The work involved development in C/C++ for both back-end and front-end, including implementing new promotions,
 fixing errors, and creating new features.
- Also worked on the development team for the new system in C#.NET to eventually replace the older software.

TOTVS

Research and Development Technician - Jul 2012 - Jul 2014

 Developed a virtual machine in C/C++ and QT for the company's proprietary language (ADVPL). Solved compilation and execution problems, created projects using CMake. Daily team meetings for clarification and activity planning.

Academic Background

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering

Languages

Portuguese: Native
 English: Fluent
 French: Intermediate
 Italian: Beginner